Voices UP021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Voices
1980 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Asian American Center
UP021
0.25 Linear Feet
1 Volumes
32 Digital Object(s)
1.16 Gigabytes
This collection contains issues of Voices, a student literary publication published by the Tufts Asian community.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Voices, a student literary publication published annually and semiannually by the Tufts Asian community.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by TASC, 2018 -- 2021, accessions UP-2018-044, UP-2019-075, and UP-2021-049.
- Voices, 1980 -- 2021; UP021.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 32 Digital Object(s); 1.16 Gigabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Voices, the student literary publication of the Tufts Asian community.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Voices, 1980; UP021.002.00001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_0eb96e7834e7d9a09738e651cddd8626)
    An Asian American literary & art magazine
    Asian American periodicals; Student publications
  - Voices, 1982; UP021.001.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_0eb96e7834e7d9a09738e651cddd8626)
  - Voices, 1984; UP021.001.002.00001.00001; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 2)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by TASC, 2018, accession UP-2018-044.
  - Voices, Spring, 1985; UP021.001.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_0eb96e7834e7d9a09738e651cddd8626)
  - Voices, Spring, 1986; UP021.001.002.00001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Spring, 1987; UP021.001.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 32 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_0eb96e7834e7d9a09738e651cddd8626)
  - Voices, Spring, 1988; UP021.001.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 25 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_0eb96e7834e7d9a09738e651cddd8626)
  - Voices, Spring, 1989; UP021.001.002.00001.00003; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 26 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Spring, 1990; UP021.001.002.00002.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 2)
    Volume
    X
  - Voices, Spring, 1991; UP021.001.001.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_0eb96e7834e7d9a09738e651cddd8626)
  - Voices, Spring, 1992; UP021.001.001.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 43 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_0eb96e7834e7d9a09738e651cddd8626)
  - Voices, Spring, 1993; UP021.001.001.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 41 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_0eb96e7834e7d9a09738e651cddd8626)
  - Voices, 1995; UP021.001.002.00002.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, 1996; UP021.001.002.00002.00004; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, circa 1998; UP021.001.002.00002.00005; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Spring, 1999; UP021.001.002.00002.00006; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, 2000; UP021.001.002.00003.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Spring, 2002; UP021.001.002.00003.00003; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, circa 2006; UP021.001.002.00003.00004; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Spring, 2008; UP021.001.002.00003.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Spring, 2009; UP021.001.002.00003.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Spring, 2010; UP021.001.002.00004.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 2)
    An Asian American Literary Magazine
  - Voices, Spring, 2011; UP021.001.002.00004.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - RacEd, 2012; ASpace_CUID; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.813 Megabytes
    Special issue procuded by Voices, an Asian American literary & art magazine
  - Voices, 2013; UP021.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes
    Transferred by TASC, 2019, accession UP-2019-075.
  - Voices, 2014; UP021.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes
  - Borders, Spring, 2016; UP021.000031
  - Voices, Spring, 2017; UP021.001.002.00004.00004; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Fall, 2017; UP021.001.002.00004.00005; 1 Folder(s); 1 Digital Object(s); 29 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Voices, Spring 2019; UP021.000032; 97.0 Megabytes
  - Voices, Spring 2020; UP021.000033; 196 Megabytes
    Online edition.
  - Voices, Spring 2020; UP021.000034; 354 Megabytes
    Print edition.
  - Voices, Spring 2021; UP021.000035; 26.3 Megabytes